http://legal.conair.com/content/page/do-not-sell-request?referrer=www.conair.com

CCPA:
Do Not Sell My Personal Information
Please follow the instructions in this form to opt-out of the sale of your personal information.
Conair values your privacy. Our Privacy Practices: For general information about how we handle personal information of California residents and a description of all of your rights under the CCPA, please visit our Privacy Policy and the section on Important Information for California Residents
Sale:
California residents have the right to opt-out of the “Sale” of their personal information. California defines the term “Sale” broadly, and includes our selling, renting, releasing, disclosing, disseminating, making available, transferring or otherwise communicating (collectively a “Sale”) of your personal information to a third party for monetary or other valuable consideration. For general information about our sale of personal information and more details about your right to opt-out of any Sale, please click here. Conair does not sell your data for monetary compensation (e.g., we do not sell lists of our users to non-affiliated third parties for their own marketing use). We allow entities to place cookies on our websites and mobile applications to collect information about your interaction with our websites and applications, including whether you make a purchase of one of our products on a different website. This collection of information may be a “Sale” under the broad definition of “Sale” as defined under the CCPA.
Opt-out Instructions:
To opt-out of sharing with targeted advertisers, please visit optout.aboutads.info and optout.networkadvertising.org.
Questions: If you have questions about this form or your rights, please contact us at privacy@conair.com.
